Marharyta Pryshchapionak



Personal Info

Address: Wrocław

Phone (WhatsApp, Telegram, Viber)

+48 796-027-535

E-mail: margokomilfo.dev@gmail.com

Nationality

Belarusian, permanent residence in Poland with a work permit

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3 (SASS/LESS)
- JavaScript
- **TypeScript**
- React, React/Redux
- RestAPI
- CSS Modules
- TDD, Snapshot Testing
- Storybook
- MaterialUI
- GitHub, GIT
- Photoshop, CorelDraw
- good communication and teamwork skills
- adaptability and quick-learning
- conflict resolution
- decision making
- time management
- ability to work under pressure
- self-motivation

Languages

Russian	••••	(native)
Belorussian	••••	(native)
Polish	••••	(B1-B2)
English	••000	(A2-B1)

Front-end (react) developer – that is what I have been going with confident small steps the past 2 years. Daily work on yourself, pumping my skills, learning English and reading technical literature helps me get closer to my goal every day. Easy? No. Nevertheless, I am ready for difficulties. Ready to learn and develop. Now I am writing with some projects to demonstrate and consolidate my skills. Its underway - the functionality is expanding, errors are being fixed.

CV – https://margokomilfo-dev.github.io/my-cv/ GitHub: https://github.com/Margokomilfo-dev

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/marharyta-pryshchapionak-b6846b1a4 Codewars: https://www.codewars.com/users/Margokomilfo-dev

In Poland, I have a permanent place of residence with access to work like local residents. I am a hardworking and goal-oriented person with a great motivation to achieve high results and become a highly qualified professional.

My main goal at work is to do more than anyone expects from me and grow as a professional together with the company. I would like to join your team and I believe that together we will be able to make this world a better place.

Work experience

"IT-incubator" (Belarus) 09.2020 current

Position: Front-end developer

JavaScript, TypeScript, React/Redux, RestAPI.

- writing web-projects
- mentoring of students
- problem solving with code and fixing of code-bugs

03.2015-12.2018

Online store "Krasotka-pro" (Belarus)

Position: Director

- internet sales
- marketing
- online support
- financial management
- problem solving

The shop was closed due to moving to Poland.

08.2011 -08,2017

Polotsk State University (Belarus), **Faculty of Information Technology**

Position: Teacher of programing languages

Teaching next subjects:

- Pascal
- Delphi
- HTML, CSS
- **JavaScript**
- accounting program 1C.

I was the main teacher of 30 testimony projects.

Interests

- foreign languages
- family
- codewars, habr, stackoverflow
- reading books
- doing sport
- travelling
- healthy way of life
- sweets and coffee ©

06.2010 -"Felix" (Belarus) 10.2012

Position: Front-end developer

- creating of web-sites
- web-design (Photoshop)
- HTML, CSS

Education

08.2006 - Polotsk State University (Belarus), 06.2011 **Faculty of Information Technology**

Specialization: Information Technology

Profession: software engineer

08.2008 -Polotsk State University (Belarus), 06.2011 **Low Faculty**

Postgraduate studies

Specialization: Lawyer Profession: lawyer

Self-education

2020 React for middle

- TypeScript (in process)

- Ant Design
- Appolo GraphQL
- Socket.IO
- Angular
- MaterislUI
- RestAPI
- Vanilla JS
- Node.js
- Jest
- Snapshot Testing
- Storybook

2020 React/Redux

- Props (attributes)
- Components
- Class Components
- State
- Methods of lifecycle
- create-react-app
- bind
- Babel, ECMAScript
- Presentational & ContainerComponents
- redux-thunk
- state vs Redux
- HOC
- React Hooks
- useReducer
- useMemo, useCallback
- useSelector, useDispatch
- connect

2019	Web developer 2.0 - HTML5 - CSS3(BEM, SASS, Bootstrap) - JavaScript (HTML DOM) - Git/GitHub - Libraries jQuery, React, Redux - Website testing - Animation Web-developer - HTML/CSS/Less/Saas - Bootstrap
2019	 Javascript jQuery WordPress Responsive web design (RWD) JavaScript + React
2016	Online- course HTML/CSS + JavaScript
2015	HTML, css, javascript
09.2012 - 11.2012	Pedagogical course
2012 2010 2009	Driving license (category B) CorelDraw Photoshop